Register of the Papers of A. E. Dick Howard for the Virginia Commission for Constitutional Revision 1969-1971
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Newspaper Clippings and Published Material
  - CCR Published Materials
    - "Full Text of the Proposed Constitutional Amendments" (Box 35)
    - State Constitutional Revision, and West Virginia Law Review, vol. 72 (Box 35)
    - The Constitution of Virginia: Report on the Commission for the Constitution (Box 35)
    - Howard: "Constitution Revision...," University of Richmond Law Review, vol. 9, no. 1 (Box 35)
      Also a tape of an October 7, 1972 radio broadcast discussion of the new constitution; panelists were AEDH, James Brownell and Charles Waddell
    - Published Research Materials (Box 36-37)
      Lists available in cartons
  - Photograph Collection
    - Subject 1969
    - CCR Members 1969, 3 photos
    - CCR Members with Counsel, 2 photos
    - Presentation of Final Report 1969, 21 photos
    - Convention of 1820-1830, photo of watercolor by George Catlin 1969, 1 photo
    - Feb. 18; AEDH photo 1969
    - AEHD photo n.d.
    - Virginia Constitution of 1776 n.d., 1 photo